CURRICULUM VITAE

FULL NAME DATE AND PLACE OF BIRTH CONTACT INFO GLUSCHKOFF, Kia Emilia 04 July 1979, Helsinki kia.gluschkoff@gmail.com

Dr. Gluschkoff has a PhD in Psychology from the University of Helsinki. She is an experienced researcher and statistician with a background in work psychology, mental health research, and data analysis. Dr. Gluschkoff is skilled in applying advanced statistical techniques and data visualization tools to solve complex research problems and has in-depth experience with many statistical softwares.

CURRENT POSITION

Senior specialist (statistics), Finnish Institute of Occupational Health	04/2021-
EDUCATION AND TRAINING	
PhD, Psychology, University of Helsinki MSc, Organization and Management, School of Business, Aalto University MSc, Psychology, University of Helsinki	2017 2014 2005
PREVIOUS PROFESSIONAL APPOINTMENTS	
Postdoctoral researcher, Finnish Institute for Health and Welfare, Finland Project: Towards socially inclusive digital society: Transforming service culture (DigiIN, PI Tarja Heponiemi)	10/2019-03/2021
University lecturer (part-time, 50% (30% 10-12/2019)) Department of Psychology and Logopedics, Discipline of Psychology, Faculty of Medicine, University of Helsinki	01/2019-12/2019
Postdoctoral researcher (part-time, 50%) Department of Psychology and Logopedics, Discipline of Psychology, Faculty of Medicine, University of Helsinki. Project: "Heterogeneity of depression at symptom level: Specific versus general patterns in etiology, development, and disability" (PI Markus Jokela).	01/2019-10/2019
Postdoctoral researcher Department of Psychology and Logopedics, Discipline of Psychology, Faculty of Medicine, University of Helsinki. Project "Computational discovery modeling for psychiatric diagnostics" (PIs Tom Rosenström and Markus Jokela).	01/2018-12/2018
Postdoctoral researcher Department of Psychology, Faculty of Education, University of Oulu. Project "Childhood antecedents and adulthood outcomes of	09/2017-12/2017
dispositional compassion" (PI Mirka Hintsanen). Doctoral student, researcher Department of Psychology and Logopedics, Discipline of Psychology,	12/2014-08/2017

TECHNICAL SKILLS

R programming, Stata, Mplus, SPSS

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Finnish: native speaker English: excellent Swedish: good

MEMBERSHIPS IN SCIENTIFIC SOCIETIES

Finnish Health Psychology Association (board member)

Faculty of Medicine, University of Helsinki.